Guide to the Graphics collection, 1740-1995 MS2379
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, 1740-1995; Series 1
  - Clarkson in 1811 by William Hazlitt; engraved by T.S. Engleheart., Circa [199-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Reproduced from: Thomas Clarkson, a biography / Ellen Gibson Wilson. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1990.; Title from handwritten notes on verso of photographic printing.; Thomas Clarkson, bust.
  - George Washington by Horatio Greenough., Circa [199-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1452
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Reproduction from: Sculpture in America / Wayne Craven. New and revised edition Newark: University of Delaware Press, 1984.; Statue of George Washington seated by Horatio Greenough, as it looks in the Smithsonian Institution.
  - Stephen Decatur by Gilbert Stuart., Circa [199-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1453
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Reproduced from an unidentified 20th century book.; Gilbert Stuart portrait of Stephen Decatur.
  - Washington, D.C.: American scenery., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1454
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; United States Capitol, side view.
  - The Capitol: American views., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 10 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1455
    Cataloging notes: "No. 70."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; United States Capitol, side view.
  - U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C. by W.M. Chase., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, hand color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1456
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; United States Capitol and lawn in front; several carriages shown.
  - United States Capitol, Washington, D.C., U.S.A.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1457
    Cataloging notes: "5."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the United States Capitol. One man shown in foreground.
  - The U.S. Capitol photographed by Bell and Brother., Circa [1868]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1458
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. Capitol shown from the side.
  - U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.: American views by W.M. Chase., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1459
    Cataloging notes: "No. 1202."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. Capitol in Washington, D.C.; front view; wings not shown.
  - The Capitol, Washington, D.C., U.S.A.., Circa [ 1920]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: sterograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1460
    Cataloging notes: "224."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the United States Capitol; several people shown in foreground; several cars shown.
  - U.S. Capitol, west front, Washington, D.C. by A.J. Fisher., Circa [1876?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1461
    Cataloging notes: "6."; Date from pencil notation on verso.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; West front of the U.S. Capitol; trees in foreground.
  - The U.S. Capitol by J.F. Jarvis., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1462
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the U.S. Capitol, seen from the side.
  - United States Captiol, Washington, D.C.: original building and dome., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1463
    Cataloging notes: East front of the U.S. Captiol, seen from side.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
    United States Captiol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - U.S. Capitol, east view, Washington, D.C.., Circa [ 1890]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1467
    Cataloging notes: "1175."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East view of the U.S. Capitol.
  - Capitol at Washington, D.C., U.S.A.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1468
    Cataloging notes: "224."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the United States Capitol; several men in foreground.
  - Senate front, Washington., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1469
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the U.S. Capitol building, seen from the side.
  - U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.: Youth's companion., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1470
  - Capitol, Washington, D.C.: American views., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1471
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; West front of the U.S. Capitol with trees in foreground.
  - Inaugural procession as seen from the White House, 1893 by B.W. Kilburn., Circa [1893]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1472
    Cataloging notes: "7906."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Inaugural procession on Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, D.C. for President Grover Cleveland.
    Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 Inauguration, 1893 Pictorial works.; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00009698; 1893 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration Pictorial works.; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; Pennsylvania Avenue (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Washington (D.C.) Pennsylvania Avenue. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01316780; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Pension Building (inaugural ball room) Washington, D.C.., Circa [1893?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1473
    Cataloging notes: "189."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Pension Building decorated for inaugural ball for Grover Cleveland.
    Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 Inauguration, 1893 Pictorial works.; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00009698; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00669375; 1893 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration Pictorial works.; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Ohio: "All hail to the good old flag," Washington, D.C., U.S.A. by B.F. Singley., Circa [1897]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1474
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Ohio veterans marching up Pennsylvania Avenue for the inauguration of President William McKinley.
  - The former home of General Robert E. Lee: Arlington National Cemetery, Va., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1475
    Cataloging notes: "32257."; "44."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Arlington House, former home of Robert E. Lee, in Arlington, Va., seen from the side.
    Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870 Homes and haunts Pictorial works.; Arlington House, the Robert E. Lee Memorial (Va.) Pictorial works.; Arlington National Cemetery (Va.) Pictorial works.
  - Lincoln Memorial, Washington, D.C.., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1476
    Cataloging notes: "26334."; "H151."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Lincoln Memorial in Washington, D.C. seen from the front. Several people on steps. Memorial was dedicated in 1922.
  - The Lincoln Memorial: when the cherries are in bloom, Washington, D.C., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1477
    Cataloging notes: "19."; "26863."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Lincoln Memorial, Washington, D.C., seen in the distance, framed by cherry trees.
  - Genl. Lee's old homestead, Arlington, Va. by J.F. Jarvis., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1478
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Arlington House, former home of Robert E. Lee, in Arlington, Va., seen from the side.
  - U.S. Treasury Building, Washington, D.C., U.S.A.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1479
    Cataloging notes: "219."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Treasury Building, in use since 1838, and located at 15th and Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., Washington, D.C.; front view.
  - Crawford bronze door: views of Washington and vicinity., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1480
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Bronze door in the the east portico of the North or Senate extension of the U.S. Capitol in Washington, D.C.
  - Marble Room in U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.., Circa [189-?]]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1482
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Interior view of a room in the U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.; marble columns, chairs, table, and chandelier shown.
  - Marble Room, Washington, D.C.: American views, standard series., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1483
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Interior view of a room in the U.S. Capitol in Washington, D.C.; marble columns, chairs, table and chandelier shown.
  - Marble Room, Senate pho. by W.M. Smith., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1484
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Interior view of a room in the U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.; marble columns, chandelier, table and chairs shown.
  - Marble Room, U.S. Capitol photographed by G.D. Wakely., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 17 cm. (Box 48, Folder 39)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1485
  - The Capitol, looking south: Washington, D.C. by John P. Soule., Circa [ 1870]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 40)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1486
    Cataloging notes: "No. 1022."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Exterior view of the U.S. Capitol in Washington, D.C., looking south.
  - East front U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C. by W.M. Chase., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, hand color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 41)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1487
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.; east front view with shrubbery in foreground.
  - West Senate front, Washington, D.C.., Circa [190-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 17 cm. (Box 48, Folder 42)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1488
    Cataloging notes: "No. 297."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; West frontal view of U.S. Senate from archway.
  - United States Capitol, Washington, D.C.: Senate front., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 43)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1489
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. Capitol, Senate front view.
  - Brumidi's alligorical painting: in dome of the U.S. Capitol by J.F. Bell., Circa [1867]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 44)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1490
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Painting in the dome of the U.S. Capitol. Shows man holding rod in right hand and holding a small bag in left hand.
  - Brumidi's alligorical [sic] painting: in dome of U.S. Capitol by F.H. Bell., Circa [1867]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 45)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1491
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Painting in the dome of the U.S. Capitol. Shows woman wearing helmet, holding a spear upward in her right hand and pointing down with the left hand.
  - Group of mechanics in Brumidi's allegorical painting in dome of the Capitol: views of Washington and vicinity photographed by J.F. Jarvis., Circa [187-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 46)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1492
    Cataloging notes: "No. 22."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Shows man standing with right foot on cylinder, touching head of another man stooping in front of him in dome of the U.S. Capitol.
  - Western emigration by Leitzie: in U.S. Capitol by F.H. Bell., Circa [1867]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 47)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1493
    Cataloging notes: Painting in U.S. Capitol.
  - East front of the Capitol, from the north east: views in Washington City, D.C., Circa [ 1890]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 17 cm. (Box 48, Folder 48)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1494
    Cataloging notes: "No. 6475."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Shows east front of the United States Capitol, seen from the side.
  - East front of the Senate House, U.S. Capitol: views in Washington City, D.C., Circa [ 1890]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 17 cm. (Box 48, Folder 49)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1495
    Cataloging notes: "No. 6488."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the Senate wing of the U.S. Capitol; several people standing at the top of the steps.
  - East front of the Capitol, from the north east: views in Washington City, D.C., Circa [ 1890]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 17 cm. (Box 48, Folder 50)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1496
    Cataloging notes: "No. 6474."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the U.S. Capitol.
  - U.S. Capitol, Washington., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereo card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 51)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1497
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; East front of the United States Capitol in Washington, D.C.; seen from the side.
  - Capitol, Washington., Circa 18--?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 52)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1498
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. Capitol Building (center) west, with trees and shrubery in foreground. Picture taken from lower level.
  - The Capitol, N.E. view: Washington, D.C., Circa 18--?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 53)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1499
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. Capitol photographed from right side with construction scaffold support on first level of steps.
  - Geo. Washington's Room, Mt. Vernon, Va.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 48, Folder 54)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1500
    Cataloging notes: "23476."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Room in the Mansion House with wooden chair with cushion in foregound at the foot of a bed. A window to the left, a dresser, mirror and doorway in the background.
  - The prodigal son photographed by B.W. Kilburn., Circa [1887]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1501
    Cataloging notes: "4545."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Men and women, standing, lying around, and also sitting under amd the left of four columns.
    Prodigal son (Parable) Pictorial works.; Prodigal son (Parable) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01078126; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Brumidi's painting, dome: Capitol, Washington, D.C. by C. Seaver, Jr., photog'r., Circa [1873]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1502
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Rotunda and dome of the U.S. Capitol; group of women in upper circle and below a group of six persons including two horses.
  - Brumidi's painting, dome: the interior of U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C. by C. Seaver, Jr., photog'r., Circa [1873]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1503
    Cataloging notes: Dome of Capitol; group of women in upper circle with men below. One man in center with his right foot on canon barrel.
  - Perries [sic] victory on Lake Erie., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1504
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Nine men in a row boat with an American flag attached to the bow; one standing near the stern pointing toward the bow of the boat.
    Perry, Oliver Hazard, 17851819 Portraits.; Lake Erie, Battle of, 1813. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85044621
  - Congressional Library, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1900?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1505
    Cataloging notes: "8046."; Front and left side of Library of Congress, including front lawn with trees, and four people walking on the walkway.
  - Decorative splendor of the Entrance Hall: Congressional Library, Washington, D.C. by H.C. White Company., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1506
    Cataloging notes: "W29573 T."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Entrance hall to the Library of Congress (Washington, D.C.) with high arched portals.
  - A poem in marble columns anf frescoed walls, Congressional Library: Washington, D.C. by B.L. Singley., Circa [1903]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereo card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1507
    Cataloging notes: "No.13602."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Library of Congress upper level; from railing viewing tops of marbled columns with arched ornate vaulted ceiling.
  - Congressional Library: interior view by B.L. Singley., Circa [1898]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1508
    Cataloging notes: "8042."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Interior upward view from balcony railings of arches, ceiling and statue holding a torch in the air.
    Library of Congress Pictorial works.; Library of Congress. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00528532; Photography, Stereoscopic. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85101299; Photography, Stereoscopic. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01062006; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The conservatory (White House), Washington, D.C., U.S.A. by B.L. Singley., Circa [1898]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, hand color; 9 x 18 m. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1509
    Cataloging notes: "8040."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Conservatory of the White House, Washington, D.C.; plants and hanging baskets shown.
  - White House conservatory, Washington by William H. Rau, photographer., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1510
    Cataloging notes: "6261."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Conservatory of the White House in Washington, D.C.; ferns and hanging baskets shown.
  - In the Aztec Garden of the Pan-American Union Building, Washington, D.C.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1511
    Cataloging notes: "32243."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Aztec garden with pool at the Pan American Union building at 17th and Constitution Avenue, N.W., in Washington, D.C. Two people shown at pool.
  - National Soldiers' Home, Washington, D.C., U.S.A.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1512